[
  {
    "counter":1,
    "center":[
      53.075537,
      8.808476
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Bremen",
    "wrong":[
      "Dresden",
      "Düsseldorf",
      "Schwerin"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":2,
    "center":[
      51.225243,
      6.77643
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Düsseldorf",
    "wrong":[
      "Bremen",
      "Wiesbaden",
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":3,
    "center":[
      50.080693,
      8.239705
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Wiesbaden",
    "wrong":[
      "Potsdam",
      "Schwerin",
      "Kiel"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":4,
    "center":[
      49.233582,
      6.99548
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Saarbrücken",
    "wrong":[
      "Hannover",
      "Magdeburg",
      "Bremen"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":5,
    "center":[
      50.97787,
      11.028967
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Erfurt",
    "wrong":[
      "Wiesbaden",
      "Kiel",
      "Magdeburg"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":6,
    "center":[
      51.050266,
      13.739284
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Dresden",
    "wrong":[
      "Hamburg",
      "Stuttgart",
      "Schwerin"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":7,
    "center":[
      48.136832,
      11.576539
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"München",
    "wrong":[
      "Düsseldorf",
      "Wiesbaden",
      "Hannover"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":8,
    "center":[
      52.516983,
      13.398018
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Berlin",
    "wrong":[
      "Schwerin",
      "Erfurt",
      "Koblenz"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":9,
    "center":[
      52.131149,
      11.639579
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Magdeburg",
    "wrong":[
      "Stuttgart",
      "Dresden",
      "Erfurt"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":10,
    "center":[
      50.353353,
      7.592952
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Koblenz",
    "wrong":[
      "Düsseldorf",
      "Hamburg",
      "Magdeburg"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":11,
    "center":[
      52.400374,
      13.056441
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Potsdam",
    "wrong":[
      "Wiesbaden",
      "Dresden",
      "Stuttgart"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":12,
    "center":[
      53.627414,
      11.41505
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Schwerin",
    "wrong":[
      "Hamburg",
      "Koblenz",
      "Potsdam"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":13,
    "center":[
      52.373889,
      9.738497
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Hannover",
    "wrong":[
      "Erfurt",
      "Berlin",
      "Hamburg"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":14,
    "center":[
      54.320937,
      10.136263
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Kiel",
    "wrong":[
      "München",
      "Koblenz",
      "Stuttgart"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":15,
    "center":[
      48.775764,
      9.177591
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Stuttgart",
    "wrong":[
      "Hannover",
      "Berlin",
      "Erfurt"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":16,
    "center":[
      53.54983,
      10.00052
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Hamburg",
    "wrong":[
      "Erfurt",
      "Berlin",
      "Schwerin"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  }
]